const chm = [
{
    question: "Atomic number represents:",
    options: ["Protons", "Neutrons", "Electrons", "Mass"],
    answer: 0
},
{
    question: "Na is in group:",
    options: ["1", "2", "7", "8"],
    answer: 0
},
{
    question: "Covalent bond involves:",
    options: ["Electron transfer", "Electron sharing", "Proton sharing", "Neutron transfer"],
    answer: 1
},
{
    question: "Avogadro’s number is:",
    options: ["6.02 × 10²³", "9.8", "3.14", "1.6 × 10⁻¹⁹"],
    answer: 0
},
{
    question: "pH less than 7 means:",
    options: ["Neutral", "Basic", "Acidic", "Salt"],
    answer: 2
},
{
    question: "Ideal gas law is:",
    options: ["PV = nRT", "V = IR", "E = mc²", "F = ma"],
    answer: 0
},
{
    question: "Isotopes have same:",
    options: ["Mass number", "Neutrons", "Protons", "Electrons"],
    answer: 2
},
{
    question: "Mole measures:",
    options: ["Mass", "Volume", "Amount of substance", "Energy"],
    answer: 2
},
{
    question: "HCl is:",
    options: ["Base", "Salt", "Acid", "Metal"],
    answer: 2
},
{
    question: "Periodic table arranged by:",
    options: ["Mass", "Atomic number", "Density", "Color"],
    answer: 1
}
];